Finding Aid for Democratic Party of Michigan records, 1932-2008
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- State Chair, Democratic State Central Committee files
  - State Chairman (Zolton Ferency)
    - Topical file 1963-1967
      - Membership Plus
        - 1963-1964 (Box 10)
        - 1966 (Box 10)
      - Michigan Yearbook, projects 1965-1966 (Box 10)
      - Novelties 1966 correspondence (Box 10)
      - Programs and planning 1963 (Box 10)
      - Projects, D.S.C.C. 1965-1966 (Box 11)
      - Project Triple Play 1965 (Box 11)
      - Public Opinion Polls 1963 (Box 11)
      - Public Opinion Survey 1967 (Box 11)
      - Purpose and goals committee 1967 (Box 11)
      - Registration, D.S.C.C. Projects 1965 (Box 11)
      - Registration Information (Box 11)
      - Republican Party
        - Michigan (Box 11)
        - State Central Committee
          - Arthur G. Elliot, chairman 1963-1964 (Box 11)
          - Elly Peterson, chair 1966 (Box 11)
        - Voting record, Legislative session 1965-1966 (Box 11)
      - Resolutions, original and final draft, 3 folders (Box 11)
      - Romney, George (Box 11)
      - Special Session In the State Legislature October 1967 (Box 11)
      - Special Study Committee on Campaign Costs and Reporting (Box 11)
      - State Convention files 1964-1967
        - 1964 Convention (Fall)
          - District Caucus reports (Box 11)
        - 1967 Convention (Spring), February 18-19, 1967
          - Correspondence (Box 11)
          - Finance (Box 11)
          - Forms, 2 folders (Box 11)
          - Miscellaneous materials and instruction (Box 11)
          - Miscellanea (Box 11)
          - Officers, District (Box 11)
          - Program (Box 11)
          - Requests, convention (Box 11)
          - Resolutions
            - County conventions (Box 11)
            - District (Box 11)
            - General (Box 11)
      - State Central Committee member (Box 11)
      - Supreme Court Apportionment Suit 1965 (Box 11)
      - Traffic safety 1966 (Box 11)
      - Urban Affairs Committee 1967 (Box 11)
      - Victory Celebration (see Democrats) (Box 11)
      - Voter Identification Program 1966 (Box 11)
      - Voter Registration 1964 (Box 11)
      - William, G. Mennen-Biographical publication for Senate Campaign October 1966 (Box 11)
      - Women's Day 1968
        - 1968 Convention (Grand Rapids) (Box 11)
  - State Chairman (Sander Levin)
    - Topical files 1968
      - Academic world-relations (Box 12)
      - Agriculture committee (D.S.C.C.) (Box 12)
      - Area conferences
        - Cadillac (tentative) (Box 12)
        - Eleventh Congressional District and V-68 Cocktail Party (Box 12)
        - Kalamazoo (Box 12)
        - Saginaw (Box 12)
      - Budget (Box 12)
      - Board of Supervisors (Box 12)
      - Business and Professional Committee (Box 12)
      - By-Laws Committee (Box 12)
      - Campaign
        - 1968 File, 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Agriculture materials (Box 12)
        - Committee
          - General, 2 folders (Box 12)
          - Regional meeting (Box 12)
          - Supervisors (Box 12)
        - County and District Chairmen (Box 12)
        - County Budgets (Box 12)
        - Legislative, State
          - 1968 files, General, 2 folders (Box 12)
          - House Democratic Committee (Box 12)
        - Personnel file (Box 12)
        - Presidential, Volunteer Block Worker's Addresses (Box 12)
        - Public relations (Box 12)
        - Registration (Box 12)
        - Speakers and scheduling (Box 12)
        - Thank you's (Box 12)
      - Candidates
        See also county and legislation
        - Committee (Box 12)
        - Potential (Box 12)
      - Century files
        - Fund files, 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Club reception
          - For Hubert Humphrey (Box 12)
          - For Ted Kennedy (Box 12)
      - Citizens for Humphrey (Box 12)
      - Citizenship
        - Chrysler Program (Box 12)
        - General Motors
          - Contributions (Box 12)
          - Program (Box 12)
        - General file (Box 12)
        - Wyandotte Chemicals Corp. (Box 12)
      - Civil Rights Commission (Box 12)
      - Cleveland (Tom) and Associates (Box 12)
      - Community Action Leadership (Box 12)
      - Congressional campaign (U.S.)
        - Candidate file (Box 13)
        - Finance Committee (Box 13)
      - Conservation department (Box 13)
      - Consumer's Committee (Box 13)
      - Constitution, State of Michigan (Box 13)
      - Contribution formula (Box 13)
      - Convention
        - County convention
          - June meeting (Box 13)
          - November meeting (Box 13)
        - National
          - Arrangements, 2 folders (Box 13)
          - Delegation
            - Business (Box 13)
            - General file (Box 13)
            - Meetings (Box 13)
          - General correspondence (Box 13)
          - Miscellaneous materials, 2 folders (Box 13)
          - Passes (Box 13)
          - Platform (Box 13)
          - Positions (Box 13)
        - State
          - Platform and resolutions committee (Box 13)
          - Sixth Congressional District (Box 13)
          - August meeting (Box 13)
      - Correspondence
        - Congressional district (Box 13)
        - County (includes some 1969 material) (Box 13)
        - County chairmen and Wayne District Chairmen (Box 13)
        - General (Box 13)
      - County
        - Candidates, 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Check lists (Box 13)
        - Committees, new officers (Box 13)
        - Home rule (Box 13)
      - Data processing (Box 13)
      - Del Rio, James, State Representative (Box 13)
      - Democrats (Box 13)
      - Democratic
        - Legislative program (Box 13)
        - National Committee
          - Federal appointments (Box 13)
          - General information (Box 13)
        - State Central Committee
          - Equal Opportunity Committee (Box 13)
          - Field, Staff reports (Box 13)
          - Finance committee (Box 13)
          - Leadership (Box 13)
          - Legislative Program (Box 13)
          - Meeting minutes (Box 13)
          - National division (Box 13)
          - Organizational file, Open House for 1968 (Box 13)
          - Speaker's Bureau (Box 13)
          - V-68 Dinner (Box 13)
        - Detroit Office Location Committee (Box 13)
        - District attorney (Box 13)
        - Educational
          - Campaign (Box 13)
          - Candidates for state posts (Box 13)
        - Election
          (see also Mid-campaign reports)
          - Cavanaugh for U.S. Senator (Box 13)
          - Congressional (U.S.) (Box 13)
          - Elsmans for U.S. Senator (Box 13)
          - Livingston for Governor (Box 13)
          - Senatorial (State) (Box 13)
        - Faust, Senator William, correspondence (Box 14)
        - Field reports (Box 14)
        - Finance committee (D.S.C.C.)
          - Accounts and correspondence, miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 14)
          - Correspondence, miscellaneous (Box 14)
          - F.N.M.A. attorneys (Box 14)
          - Voluntary contributions, 2 folders (Box 14)
        - Get Out the Vote, miscellaneous material (Box 14)
        - Highway department (Box 14)
        - Ingham County Convention file (Box 14)
        - Israel-Jordan conflict (Box 14)
        - Issues conference (Box 14)
        - Jeff-Jack Dinner
          - General file, 2 folders (Box 14)
          - Luncheon on April 6th (Box 14)
        - Judicial selection, special study committee (Box 14)
        - Law enforcement and individual rights, special party committee (Box 14)
        - Legislative candidates (Box 14)
        - Levin, Sander
          - Cocktail party (Box 14)
          - Fund raisers in honor of (Box 14)
        - Membership
          - Drive for the party
            - Chairman's correspondence, 2 folders (Box 14)
            - Miscellaneous materials (Box 14)
          - Reimbursements (Box 14)
          - Reports file (Box 14)
          - Youth (Box 14)
        - MG Advertising for '68 campaign (Box 14)
        - Michigan Democrat, correspondence concerning (Box 14)
        - Mid-campaign reports, county figures (Box 14)
        - Midwest conference (Box 14)
        - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 14)
        - Officers' meeting (Box 14)
        - Operation support 1968 (Box 14)
        - Osteopathy Special subcommittee on (Box 14)
        - Platform, Michigan Democratic Party, 2 folders (Box 14)
        - Polls
          - General campaign survey (Box 15)
          - Quayle study (Box 15)
        - Political action, study committee on (Box 15)
        - Poor people's campaign (Box 15)
        - Redford Township, correspondence (Box 15)
        - Regional conferences (Box 15)
        - Regional organizational seminars (Box 15)
        - Sinatra, Frank, an evening with (Box 15)
        - Sixth Congressional District, correspondence from (Box 15)
        - Small Business Administration (SBA), Advisory Council (Box 15)
        - Swainson Farm Picnic (Box 15)
        - Talent Search, 2 folders (Box 15)
        - Teen Dems (Box 15)
        - Television, Jack Horn (Box 15)
        - Traffic Safety Committee (Box 15)
        - Victory celebration (Box 15)
        - Vietnam (Box 15)
        - Wayne Community College (Box 15)
        - Women, Michigan Federation of Democratic (Box 15)
        - Young Democrats (Box 15)
  - State Chairman (James McNeely)
    - Topical files 1968-1970
      - Anti-Ballistic Missile (A.B.M.) Committee 1969 (Box 15)
      - Agriculture Committee 1968-1970 (Box 15)
      - Business and Professional Committee 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Calendars for Party Meetings 1969-1970 (Box 15)
      - Campaign statistics 1970 (Box 15)
      - Candidate information 1970 (Box 15)
      - "Capitol Viewpoint," William Ryan, Sander Levin publication 1969 (Box 15)
      - Century fund
        - Correspondence and material relating to
          - 1968-1969 (Box 15)
          - 1970 (Box 15)
        - Correspondence, Sherrie Wilmore, secretary's file 1969, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Chairman, State
        - Biographical and other material related to J. McNeely's election as state chairman 1969-1970 (Box 15)
        - News Releases 1969-1970 (Box 15)
        - Weekly calendar 1969-1970 (Box 15)
      - Challenger credentials 1969 (Box 15)
      - Chavez, Cesar 1969 (Box 15)
      - Citizenship participation 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Computers (Box 15)
      - Committee on Utilization 1969 (Box 15)
      - Conservation 1969-1970 (Box 15)
      - Contest, fundraising for campaign, 3 folders (Box 15)
      - Contributions, Voluntary 1968-1970 (Box 15)
        (see also "Expansion of")
      - Control Data Corporation 1970 (Box 15)
      - Convention, State
        - 1968-1969 General information (Box 16)
        - February 1969 (Box 16)
        - 1970 General information (Box 16)
        - January 1970 Special convening, 2 folders (Box 16)
        - August 1970 General Information (Box 16)
        - 1970 Sherrie's file (Box 16)
      - Correspondence, general 1969 (Box 16)
      - Credentials Committee (Box 16)
      - Democratic
        - Committees In Other States 1969-1970 (Box 16)
        - National Committee 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 16)
        - State Central Committee
          - Civil Actions file (Box 16)
          - General Information files, 2 folders
            - 1969 (Box 16)
            - 1970 (Box 16)
          - House and Senate analysis (Box 16)
      - Education, Fall Strategy Committee 1969 (Box 16)
      - Election Analysis, correspondence 1969 (Box 16)
      - Executive Committee, Saturday Hearing (Box 16)
      - Field Staff
        - General 1968-1970 (Box 16)
      - Finance
        - 1969
          - Committee (Box 16)
          - General (includes 1970 Budget) (Box 16)
          - Reports, 2 folders (Box 16)
        - 1970
          - General correspondence and information (Box 16)
          - Reports (Box 16)
      - Gala, Party February 5, 1970 (Box 16)
      - Get Out the Vote 1970 (Box 16)
      - Jefferson-Jackson (Jeff-Jack) Dinner
        - General 1969 (Box 16)
        - Reports 1969 (Box 16)
      - Leadership meetings 1969, 2 folders (Box 17)
      - McNeely, James
        - Campaign bills 1969 (Box 17)
        - Personal file
          - 1968-1969 (Box 17)
          - 1969-1970 (Box 17)
        - Speech copies (Box 17)
      - Membership
        - Mailing 1969 (Box 17)
        - Reports 1969, 3 folders (Box 17)
        - Speaking tour, statewide 1969 (Box 17)
      - Moonlight Cruise 1969 (Box 17)
      - Nationalities (Box 17)
      - New Democratic Coalition (N.D.C.) 1969-1970 (Box 17)
      - Over 60 Task Force 1969 (Box 17)
      - Parochiaid 1969-1970 (Box 17)
      - Platform and Resolutions Committee 1968 (Box 17)
      - Political reform
        - Miscellaneous "Bob" file (Box 17)
        - Haber Commission, 4 folders (Box 17)
        - Lists and memorandums, 3 folders (Box 17)
      - Political Reform Commission (P.R.C.)
        - Committee files
          - General file (Box 18)
          - Committee #2, Part I report (Box 18)
          - Committee #7, reports and recommendations
            - Part I (Box 18)
            - Part II (Box 18)
            - Part III (Box 18)
        - Convention 1970 (Box 18)
        - Distribution, Summary of P.R.C. (Box 18)
        - Information on P.R.C. (Box 18)
        - News Releases (Box 18)
        - Reports
          - Final Drafts, 2 folders (Box 18)
          - Final Report (Box 18)
      - Polls
        - Quayle Campaign Survey
          - 1968 (Box 18)
          - 1969 (Box 18)
      - Porter, Paul, election in 41st District 1969 (Box 18)
      - Presidential primary 1969 (Box 18)
      - Public Relations Department 1969-1970 (Box 18)
      - Re-apportioned Precinct Delegates 1970 (Box 18)
      - Referendum 1970 (Box 18)
      - Register and Vote
        - 1968 finances (Box 18)
        - 1969 (Box 18)
      - Regional conference 1969 (Box 18)
      - Releases, Party Press (many from 1968) (Box 18)
      - Republican State Central Committee (Box 18)
      - Resolutions Committee (Box 18)
      - Rules Committee (Box 18)
      - Secretary of State-Hare (Box 18)
      - Sex education, resolution 1969 (Box 18)
      - Small Loan Bill 1969-1970 (Box 18)
      - Student Bill of Rights 1970 (Box 18)
      - Stuttman Recount 1970 (Box 18)
      - United Auto Workers (Box 18)
      - Upper Peninsula meeting May 1969 (Box 18)
    - Topical files 1971
      - Black Caucus (Box 19)
      - Blueprint for Action, McNeely Speech (Box 19)
      - Branch Manager's Listing (Box 19)
      - Business and Professional Club (Hillsdale) (Box 19)
      - Busing (Box 19)
      - Century Fund (Box 19)
      - Citizenship Participation (Box 19)
      - Civil Service Commission (Box 19)
      - Constitutional Amendments (Box 19)
      - Consumer Credit (Box 19)
      - Conservation (Box 19)
        (see League of Voters)
      - Contest, Fund Raising file 1970-1971 (Box 19)
      - Convention February 1971 (Box 19)
        (see also Precinct)
      - Democratic
        - Academic Research Council (DARC) (Box 19)
        - Clubs (Box 19)
        - Policy Committee (Box 19)
        - State Central Committee
          - By-laws and by-laws committee (Box 19)
          - Committees, membership lists (Box 19)
          - Meetings
            - General information (Box 19)
            - Resolutions Committee February 1971, 1 folders (Box 19)
            - Resolution committee proposals July 31, 1971 (Box 19)
        - State Chairmen (Box 19)
        - Women's Groups (Box 19)
      - Detroit
        - City of, correspondence, directories, etc. (Box 19)
        - Office file (Box 19)
      - Directory (Party) Distribution file (Box 19)
      - Discrimination Against Women, special party subcommittee on (Box 19)
      - Education
        (see also Michigan: Conference and Education Associations)
        - Institutions of Higher Learning
          - Community Colleges (Box 19)
          - Michigan State University (Box 19)
          - Wayne State University (Box 19)
        - State Advisory Council on Higher Education (Box 19)
        - State Board of Education (Box 19)
      - Eighteen Year Old Vote (Box 20)
      - Elections
        - Analysis of 1970 (Box 20)
        - Laws relating to (Box 20)
      - Electoral College/Electors (Box 20)
      - Executive Committee (Box 20)
      - Fan mail (Box 20)
      - Field reports (Box 20)
      - Financial
        - General file (Box 20)
        - Committees, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Levin debt (Box 20)
        - Prospects (names and addresses) (Box 20)
        - Reports (Box 20)
      - Five Hundred Club
        - 1970 (Box 20)
        - 1971 (Box 20)
      - Fundraisers, County (Box 20)
      - Grape Boycott 1970 (Box 20)
      - Griffin, Robert (Box 20)
      - Holland Plan (Box 20)
      - House
        - Bonding Issue 1970 (Box 20)
        - Resolution GG (Box 20)
      - Inauguration 1971 (Box 20)
      - Indians (Box 20)
      - Jefferson-Jackson (Jeff-Jack) Dinner, 5 folders (Box 20)
      - Jury Boards (Box 20)
      - Leadership meetings (Box 20)
      - Legislative Joint events (Box 20)
      - Letters to Editor (Box 20)
      - Lettuce boycott 1970-1971 (Box 20)
      - Liquor Control Commission (Box 20)
      - Maritime Union (Box 20)
      - McNeely, James
        - Correspondence, Post-convention (Box 20)
      - Membership
        - Chairmen (Box 20)
        - Drive fund (Box 20)
      - Michigan
        - AFL-CIO (Box 21)
        - Doctors Political Action Committee (Box 21)
        - Education Association (M.E.A.) (Box 21)
        - Jaycees (Box 21)
        - Michigan Democrat (Box 21)
        - Mississippi Alliance (Box 21)
        - Register and Vote Committee (Box 21)
        - State
          - Chamber of Commerce (Box 21)
          - Highway Commission (Box 21)
        - Trial Lawyers (Box 21)
        - Week (Box 21)
      - Oakland County Democratic Board of Supervisor's Platform (Box 21)
      - Political Reform (P.R.)
        - Continuing P.R. Committee (Box 21)
        - Correspondence (Box 21)
      - Possible
        - Committees and/or committee assignments (Box 21)
        - Staff (Box 21)
      - Precinct delegate training material (Box 21)
      - Proportional voting methods, explanation of (Box 21)
      - Race track auditors (Box 21)
      - Recommendations to the Governor (Box 21)
      - Regional workshops (Box 21)
      - Register and vote (Box 21)
        See Michigan, Register and Vote
      - Registration, voting (Box 21)
      - Republican materials (Box 21)
      - Resolutions committee (Box 21)
      - Senatorial candidates (Box 21)
      - Senior citizens (Box 21)
      - Small Loans Bill (Box 21)
      - Solex Bicycle file (Box 21)
      - Speaker's Bureau (Box 21)
      - Special Elections (54th House District) (Box 21)
      - Staff meetings (Box 21)
      - State
        - Board of canvassers (Box 21)
        - Chairman
          - Appointments, requests, confirmations (Box 21)
          - General correspondence and other information (Box 21)
      - Victory Party, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Voting methods (Box 21)
        (see Proportional voting methods)
      - Willmore, Sherrie, Secretary's file (Box 21)
      - Young
        - Democrats (Box 21)
        - Teen Democrats (Box 21)
        - Voter information (Box 21)
  - State Chairman (James McNeely/Morley Winograd)
    - Topical file 1972-1973
      - AFL-CIO (Michigan) (Box 22)
      - Association of State Democratic Chairmen (Box 22)
      - Bob (Griffin) Watchers 1972 campaign (Box 22)
      - Budgets 1973 (Box 22)
      - Business and Professional Committee (Box 22)
      - Busing 1972 (Box 22)
      - Century fund 1973 (Box 22)
      - Chicanos (Box 22)
      - Campaign
        - Budget information 1972 (Box 22)
        - Congressional, State 1972
          - General Campaign information, 3 folders (Box 22)
          - Press kit, 2 folders (Box 22)
        - Party primary practices, code of (Box 22)
        - Senatorial Committee (Box 22)
      - Clearance (Box 22)
      - Citizens Conference on State Legislatures (Box 22)
      - Congressional delegation (Box 22)
      - Consumer's Council (Michigan) (Box 22)
      - Correspondence 1972-1973 (topical)
        - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 22)
        - Michigan House of Representatives, 4 folders (Box 22)
        - Michigan State Senate (Box 22)
      - Correspondence 1972-1973 (by name)
        - Austin, Richard H. (Box 22)
        - Conyers, John, Jr. (U.S. Congressman) (Box 22)
        - Diggs, Charles, Jr. (U.S. Congressman) (Box 22)
        - Dingell, John D. (U.S. Congressman) (Box 22)
        - Ford, Gerald (Box 22)
        - Ford, William D. (U.S. Congressman) (Box 22)
        - Griffiths, Martha (Box 22)
        - Hart, Philip A. (Box 22)
        - Kelly, Frank (Box 22)
        - Koza, John Reed (Box 22)
        - Mitchell, Bob-Personnel 1968 (Box 22)
        - Nedzi, Lucien (U.S. Congressman) (Box 22)
        - O'Hara, James G. (U.S. Congressman) (Box 22)
        - Riegle, Donald W. Jr. (U.S. congressman) (Box 22)
        - Shore, Mike (Box 22)
        - Wallace, George, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - County Commissioner's meeting (Box 23)
      - Democratic
        - Appeals committee (Box 23)
        - State Central Committee
          - Agriculture Committee (Box 23)
          - Committee meetings, 2 folders (Box 23)
          - Delegates (Box 23)
          - Policy Committee People (Box 23)
          - Resolutions Committee (Box 23)
          - Rules and Political reform (Box 23)
          - Rules Committee (Box 23)
        - State Chairman
          (See also Association of)
          - General information (Box 23)
          - Speaking requests and invitations (Box 23)
        - State convention
          - 1972, 3 folders (Box 23)
          - 1973, 3 folders (Box 23)
      - Democratic National Committee, 3 folders (Box 23)
      - Democratic National Convention 1972, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Democratic sheriffs (Box 24)
      - Drug Abuse (Box 24)
      - Economy In Government Committee (Box 24)
      - Education (candidates for state posts) (Box 24)
      - Election: Laws (Box 24)
      - Election: Laws: Federal Elections Campaign Act, 3 folders (Box 24)
      - Executive Committee, membership
        - Chairman and county officers, 3 folders (Box 24)
      - Fair authority (state of Michigan) (Box 24)
      - Finance, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Finance Study Committee (Box 24)
      - Five Hundred Club (Box 24)
      - Fund raising (Box 24)
      - Gun Control (Box 24)
      - Jefferson-Jackson (Jeff-Jack) Day Dinner 1972 (Box 24)
      - Jefferson-Jackson (Jeff-Jack) Day Dinner 1973 (Box 24)
      - Leadership meetings (Box 24)
      - Leadership newsletters (Box 24)
      - Media releases (Box 24)
      - Membership 1972-1973, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Memorandums to staff, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous material, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) (Box 24)
      - Nationalities (Box 24)
      - News media (Box 24)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box 24)
      - Presidential Campaign of Senator George McGovern 1972, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Presidential Campaign of Senator George McGovern 1972, 3 folders (Box 25)
      - Register and Vote Committee (Box 25)
      - Registration, 4 folders (Box 25)
      - Resolutions received after January 16 meeting (Box 25)
      - Retail Gas Dealers (Michigan) (Box 25)
      - Senate
        - Michigan
          - Bills 698/699 (Box 25)
          - Campaign, Frank J. Kelly 1972, 3 folders (Box 25)
          - Resolutions AA and Z (Box 25)
          - Subcommittee I on Fiscal Crisis and Taxation Policies, Neil Staebler, 3 folders (Box 25)
      - Supreme Court 1972 (Box 25)
      - Taxes, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Teen Dems (Box 25)